Welcome.
And an order of fries, please.
No. No fries.
Aww...
Have a good one.
Well, should we head home?
Wait, what are you eating?!
Uh, fries?
Yeah, I can see that.
But when did you buy them?
It's fine! This is their smallest size.
It's not fine, Elfuda.
I told you not to get any...
Plus-Sized Elf
A Stagnating Dream
What a beautiful day!
It'd be a shame to waste it.
Let's get out of the house, Elfuda.
Loafing around again...
Elfuda, there's a hole in your pants.
For real?!
Warring Spuds
You're right...
Should we go buy you some new ones?
Don't worry, it won't be a problem.
I came prepared!
That's a lot of tracksuits...
Better to have 'em and
not need 'em, am I right?
Tracksuits are downright incredible!
Moisture-wicking, odor-resistant, breathable...
They do it all!
Loungewear, sleepwear, casual wear...
You can wear 'em 24/7!
And what's more...
Plain old tracksuits like these are the
unofficial uniform of couch potatoes everywhere!
Can you see the a-peel?!
Now you're just reaching...
Anyway, hurry up and
get changed so we can go.
This weather is way too nice
to stay cooped up inside.
Alright, alright.
You're so impatient sometimes...
Don't just start undressing in front of me!
And up we go!
Human, please don't
mention this to Bubble Butt...
Gotcha.
Try our fresh French fries!
Hey, wait...
This is the place with the French fries
everyone raves about.
But you'll spoil your dinner.
Yeah, but... after a long run...
Fine, I'll make you a healthy potato dish.
Just hold out till then.
Thanks a bunch, human!
Massage Relaxation
Good morning!
So what's new?
I've been doing the stretches you taught me.
Pragmatic as always...
SQUISH
Your muscles are so tense.
I'm on my feet all day. It's not my fault.
Your calves are especially tight!
The rain...!
My gills could do with the extra moisture...
Should we wait inside the clinic?
Welcome! Do you have an appointment?
Yup!
Wheeze, wheeze
Twitch, twitch
All done.
Until next time then...
Our turn yet?
Great timing. I just finished
Kuroeda's treatment.
Wow, you're drenched.
Goes to show her circulation's getting better.
C'mon, squeeze me real good too!
Shouldn't you take a break first?
It's okay. I'm going on my break after this.
Your hips are especially tight...
Ah, the tenderloin.
Your back, too...
Ah, the sirloin.
Please don't equate her anatomy
to different cuts of pork.
Yeah!
I'm not as cute as a precious little piggy!
I've got a spare pair of pants
I can lend you...
My goodness, are you okay?
I'm not a big fan of thunder...
I nearly forgot.
It was raining when we got here.
I'm real sorry!
Oh dear, it's perfectly fine.
Could I trouble you for a spare shirt too?
S-sure!
Nooooo!
The cyclops reverted to her natural size?!
Thunder scary...!
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf.
Naoe! Your next client is here!
Oh, sorry, but...
Would you mind giving me a few-
Aww, who's a good girl?!
You seem pretty tense!
We'd better work out all these knots!
I'm heading out!
I had a ton of clients today...
Thanks for coming to see me, Laika.
But maybe try to show up
in human form next time, yeah?
The health deparment has
a thing about dogs...
'Kay, see you later!
Hey, you.
Yes?
Urk-!
Take it easy.
There's no need to be suspicious of me.
Well now I'm suspicious...
I have a favor to ask.
Would you be willing to hear me out?
Sorry, but I'm kind of in a hurry...
It will only take a moment.
It's about the foolish elven girl
who's been residing at your apartment.
Let's speak elsewhere. Follow me.
Who ARE you...?
This so-called "soft serve"
is a delicious treat.
Huh?
It's as cold as ice and extremely sweet.
The fact that you can access
this delicacy whenever you want...
It seems your world has some
very advanced technology.
A-are you...?
There is no conflict here.
It's peaceful.
Comfortable, even.
I understand why she wouldn't want to leave.
Don't panic, human!
E-Elfuda?!
Lately I haven't been able to shake the feeling
that someone was watching us...
but I guess it wasn't the satyr.
Who the hell are you?!
Take off that mask!
Honestly...
The human and I were simply
having a conversation.
You're as shallow-minded as ever, aren't you?
YOU...!
Haven't seen you in a while,
you rude little brat.
Auntie?!
She's your aunt?!
What a heartfelt reunion.
The arrow was a nice touch.
I-I'm sowwy...!
"I haven't heard from my
good-for-nothing daughter.
Track her down for me," your mother said...
Ow-ow-ow...!
...but just look at all this blubber.
It's not that you WON'T come home,
it's that you CAN'T.
Your mother was worried sick.
Ouch...
Um, there's no need to be violent...
You haven't even seen "violent" yet.
Getting a little lax happens to the best of us,
but THIS level of flab is inexcusable.
Despite my insistence that you
correct your behavior,
you've continued to demonstrate
a lack of discipline.
W-well, I...
Human.
Yes?
I'm going to be staying at
your apartment for a while too.
What?
Auntie's my mentor. She taught me
how to handle myself in combat.
No gathering firewood or drawing water...
This technology is convenient.
Once her mind is made up,
she won't listen to anyone.
I apologize.
It's okay. That's not what bothers me...
Is she here to bring you back home?
Yes.
I had every intention of
returning in my own time...
But since I can't pass through the gate,
she'll probably give up and leave.
Let's worry about it in the morning.
Wake up.
How long do you plan on sleeping
with that unsightly belly poking out?
Go get dressed and ready.
Ready? For what?
Pick up the pace!
But I don't have the energy...
'cause I'm hungry...
Alright, fine.
Here.
What's that?
Breakfast.
You'll be reducing your portion sizes and
training with me for the foreseeable future.
What?!
If I hear any complaints, you get nothing.
I'm starving...
Finish eating.
We're going another 5 kilometers.
What's this about?
Human...
Even I can tell you're a good person.
I also realize that your world is
one of ease and comfort.
However, that doesn't necessarily
result in being a good influence.
Wh-what are you getting at...?
This world is soft.
And that softness has turned her
into a spoiled crybaby.
Listen, human.
From now on, she's my responsibility.
You're too soft, so I'll be taking over.
The one person who knows
what's best for her... is me.
B-but...!
She WILL lose weight
and she'll do it MY way.
She'll never stand on her own two feet
as long as you're around.
So you'll back off, yes?
Next up is strength training!
There's no time to rest!